<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Embracing Medellín on Uprooted: Venezuelan Families Flee to Colombia</title>
    <link>/photo-stories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Embracing Medellín on Uprooted: Venezuelan Families Flee to Colombia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 13:14:40 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/photo-stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Home</title>
      <link>/photo-stories/chap2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 21:34:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photo-stories/chap2/</guid>
      <description>After leaving behind their home country, where most Venezuelan immigrants spent their entire lives, families are forced to start over. Migrants find new places to live wherever they can around the city. Some live night to night in different inquilinatos, while others live in rented apartments and others still find one-room homes to buy. In most cases there is not enough room for families to sleep comfortably.
&amp;ldquo;We feel satisfied because we’re sharing with the biggest group of the family, which is the grandkids, and we keep fighting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What They Carry</title>
      <link>/photo-stories/chap1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 21:34:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photo-stories/chap1/</guid>
      <description>As resources dwindle, violence erupts, and corruption becomes rampant, Venezuelans cope with the reality of leaving their home. They are forced to leave nearly everything behind in search of a safer life. However, some items are held near and dear as families and individuals escape the turmoil that has overridden their country. Venezuelans hold these items close to their heart while they hope for the day that their country will return to peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/photo-stories/chap3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photo-stories/chap3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/photo-stories/chap4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photo-stories/chap4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>