<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Embracing Medellín on Uprooted: Venezuelan Families Flee to Colombia</title>
    <link>/photo-stories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Embracing Medellín on Uprooted: Venezuelan Families Flee to Colombia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 13:14:40 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/photo-stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What They Carry</title>
      <link>/photo-stories/chap1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 21:34:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photo-stories/chap1/</guid>
      <description>As resources dwindle, violence erupts, and corruption becomes rampant, Venezuelans cope with the reality of leaving their home. They are forced to leave nearly everything behind in search of a safer life. However, some items are held near and dear as families and individuals escape the turmoil that has overridden their country. Venezuelans hold these items close to their heart while they hope for the day that their country will return to peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Home</title>
      <link>/photo-stories/chap2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 21:34:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photo-stories/chap2/</guid>
      <description>After leaving behind their home country, where most Venezuelan immigrants spent their entire lives, families are forced to start over. Migrants find new places to live wherever they can around the city. Some live night to night in different inquilinatos, while others live in rented apartments and others still find one-room homes to buy. In most cases there is not enough room for families to sleep comfortably.
&amp;ldquo;We feel satisfied because we’re sharing with the biggest group of the family, which is the grandkids, and we keep fighting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Family, Together</title>
      <link>/photo-stories/chap3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 21:34:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photo-stories/chap3/</guid>
      <description>After traveling hundreds of miles on foot, a group of five Venezuelans, who together call themselves a family, arrived in Medellin on February 27th. Before leaving their homes, they all held different, honest jobs including food service and hair care but were all laid off over the course of the last year due to a crumbling economy. Now in Colombia, the family works 15 hour days asking for money in exchange for small candies on the street in order to make enough money to afford food and a tiny room to sleep in each night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making it in Medellín</title>
      <link>/photo-stories/chap4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 21:34:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photo-stories/chap4/</guid>
      <description>Creating a new life in a new country is no easy feat, especially for the Venezuelan people. Many of these immigrants in Colombia strike an uphill, as their journeys have faced many obstacles in their search to restart or preserve their way of life. This dream of success isn’t impossible, however. These Venezuelans have done just that; whether it be living life without debt for the first time or preserving a family business, these Venezuelans have found a way to survive for their families.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>